Right now, we want to stretch our hands for deliverance, if there are any evil people
because there are some of them that would resist because of their nature.
Many are here for deliverance and many are not ready for deliverance,
unless we force that deliverance on them.
Many don't even know that they have evil powers because they are being used.
They don't know. They say, "I'm a Christian", they can speak in tongues, they can do this...
They don´t even know that they have an evil spirit.
They keep using their body; they don't know.
There are people like that.
If you now ordinarily say, "You are a witch", they will take you to any level,
that you spoil their name, you do this.
It is only the power of God that can expose this.
So also, we have some people here that know that they have this power
and they are here for deliverance and they are ready to submit and surrender.
Also, we have some - they know they have evil power and they are here,
they are not ready to surrender; they are here for a test, trial.
So, we have different people like that.
Like one woman in our midst here that killed her husband. Please, come out.
It's not just killing like that; the whole thing is a mystery.
Mystery in the sense that she slept, carried a cutlass and by the time she cut,
it turned into her husband and the husband died in the dream.
By the time she woke up, her husband became sick.
The husband would say that this is the dream he had,
that somebody carried a cutlass and cut his head off.
And the wife would say, "I was the one who cut your head off. I'm sorry".
What can we say about this?
In cases like that, she is being used.
Come out. Jesus loves you.
Before we open our mouth and begin to ask for this deliverance,
voluntarily, you can just come out before we start the prayer.
Did This Lady Actually KILL Her Own Husband???
Who are you?
Please, Man of God, I dreamt and I was given a knife.
I took the knife and killed my husband.
I want deliverance please.
What happened in the dream?
I was in a dream, when I saw my husband coming out.
I was holding a knife and cut his neck.
After cutting his neck, when you woke up, what happened?
Two months after that, the man died.
I want to tell you that she is just being used; she is not a witch.
They are just using her.
Those who are doing it, they are somewhere else.
They are just using that to destroy her.
But as a man of God, I will pray for you.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ, out!
Jesus!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Okay. Shout the name Jesus.
Jesus!
Watch your screen and see what is happening to her
after she shouted the name Jesus Christ.
The name that is above all names. Down she goes.
She is free.
Glory be to God in the highest.
She has been set free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
PROPHECY CONFIRMATION
My name is Patricia Fabian. I come from Akwa Ibom State.
Now, can you tell us who the young man standing beside you is?
He is my son.
Okay. Can you tell us the prophecy you received from the man of God during the service.
After the first service...
During the second service, the man of God prophesied that there is a woman
who killed her husband and it is a mystery.
So, I came out and told him that it is me.
Okay. What did the man of God also say after he gave this word of prophecy?
He also prophesied that it was in a dream that I killed the man -
I didn't open my eyes - that someone used me to kill the man.
He said that it was after I had cut the man's neck that he fell sick and later died.
There is one woman in our midst here that killed her husband.
Please, come out.
It is not just killing like that; the whole thing is a mystery.
Mystery in the sense that she slept, carried a cutlass
and by the time she cut, it turned into her husband and the husband died in the dream.
By the time she woke up, her husband became sick.
It is true because the man of God was not there when I had the dream.
And after the man of God gave this message of prophecy, what happened?
He delivered me.
So you mean, the man of God delivered you after he had given you this prophecy?
Yes.
Okay, can we hear from your son?
Tell us your name.
My name is Cosmas Fabian.
I am from Akwa Ibom State.
And the woman beside you?
She is my mother.
So were you in the church today when the man of God prophesied concerning your mother?
Yes, I was in the church and I believe the prophecy - it is true.
What did the man of God say in his prophecy to your mum?
He said that there was a woman that was being used and it was mysterious;
that she was used to kill her husband in a dream.
And the man of God also said when the husband woke up, what happened?
He said that he fell sick and that led to his death.
I believe the prophecy because we knew that she was possessed.
That is why we came with her.
Today, we are happy that she has been delivered.
To God be the glory. We thank God Almighty for the deliverance your mother has received
today after the prophecy from the anointed man of God.
We want to pray with her that God Almighty will continue to strengthen her
and give her the grace to make the Word of God the standard for her life
so that the deliverance she has received today will be permanent in her life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank you very much
Mrs Patricia Afebi Aneke came back to The SCOAN after the 2nd Sunday Service that she was delivered and she is blessed with the sum of 200,000 Naira with the gift of Holy Bible and 4 bags of rice by Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV team. Glory be to God.
Only Jesus can determine if your sin is greater than her own.
Tell your neighbour.
One thing is clear: All have sinned.
Our Lord Jesus Christ that says, "Thou shalt not lie against your neighbour",
also says, "Thou shalt not kill".
If you have now lied against your neighbour, you have killed.
Let's come together and restore her back.
We will give her 200,000 Naira.
Give them four bags of rice each to take home. Thank you.
Hallelujah!
You should see giving as the reason for relationship
Just as receiving is the reason for a relationship as well
When we give, we receive
More of whatever we give
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Patricia Fabian and I come from Akwa Ibom State.
We want you to share with us your testimony; what God has done in your life.
My testimony of what God has done in my life is:
Last Sunday, during the second service,
the man of God prophesied that there is a woman over there
who was used by an evil spirit to kill her husband; she should come out.
So I came out.
When I came out, the man of God said that I am not the one who intentionally did it;
that I am not a witch, and that it was an evil spirit that used me to kill my husband.
There is one woman in our midst here, that killed her husband.
Please, come out.
It is not just killing like that; the whole thing is a mystery.
Mystery in the sense that she slept, carried a cutlass
and by the time she cut, it turned into her husband and the husband died in the dream.
By the time she woke up, the husband became sick.
Now that the man of God has delivered me from that bondage, I'm very happy.
The bad dreams I usually had, after my deliverance, I don't have them anymore.
I'm very happy and I'm free now.
You mean, since the man of God prayed for you and you were delivered,
all those bad dreams are gone?
They are gone - no more again.
Now tell us more about what God Almighty did in your life today in the service.
This afternoon, during the time of the second service,
I was surprised when the man of God gave me a gift of N200,000 and the Holy Bible
to use in the church and to continue reading and repent.
I'm very happy because when my husband died, everything was very difficult for me
to look after my small children and to pay for our house because our building has problems.
We used to spent money for the upkeep of the house.
I am very happy for receiving these gifts from the man of God.
I thank the man of God so much and may God bless him.
May God give him long life to help the poor and widows like me.
I am very, very happy.
He gave me four bags of rice, the Holy Bible and N200,000.
I am very, very happy about his gift.
PROPHECY CONTINUES
There is a lady that I met at the emergency here.
TT: Jacqueline Margaret
RV: Mel Flowers 01/09/2018